Finding Aid for the Ayres & Fiege Architectural Drawings LSC.0115
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 5: Residential projects., 1939-1970
  - Subseries B: Private homes., 1939-1970.; 73 map folders
    - (3 of 5)., 1948 (Folder 124)
      - Polster residence., 1948.; 5.; 4 items.
        Job Number 704. Polster residence
        143 Addison Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Leonard H. Polster.
    - (4 of 5)., 1948 (Folder 125)
      - Wynn residence., 1948.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 705. Wynn residence
        23010 Victory Blvd. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Russ Wynn.
      - Palermo residence II., 1948.; 2.; 1 item.
        Job Number 709. Palermo residence II
        12823 Landale St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. G. Palermo.
      - Shura residence., 1948.; 3.; 8 items.
        Job Number 715. Shura residence
        4619 White Oak Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. Shura.
      - Squillace residence., 1948.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 721. Squillace residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Faust Squillance.
      - Kennedy residence., 1948.; 5.; 5 items.
        Job Number 726. Kennedy residence
        Round Valley Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. O. Kennedy.
    - (5 of 5)., 1948 (Folder 126)
      - Miner residence., 1948.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 727. Miner residence
        Murietta Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, details, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Guy Miner.
      - Bender residence II., 1948.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 729. Bender residence II
        14061 Roblar Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Dave & Jack Bender.
      - Porter residence., 1948.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 730. Porter residence
        12523 Huston St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Gene Porter.
      - Bell residence., 1948.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 731. Bell residence
        Dixie Canyon Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Thos. Bell.
      - Green duplex., 1948.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 738. Green duplex
        S.E. corner of 4th and Central, Fillmore, CA.
        Original drawings: plan, elevations and section.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. A.T. Green.
    - (1 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 127)
      - Moore residence & garage., 1949.; 1.; 2 items.
        Moore residence & garage
        11056 Valerio, North Hollywood, CA. (?)
        Owner: Mr. J. R. Moore.
      - Poppenhusen residence., 1949.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 735. Poppenhusen residence (English Farmhouse)
        Franklin Canyon Dr. Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations, sections, perspective and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H.C. Poppenhusen.
      - Sprague residence., 1949.; 3.; 15 items.
        Job Number 736. Sprague residence
        N.E. corner of Gloria Ave. and Valley Vista Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. G. T. Sprague.
    - (2 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 128)
      - Ladouceur residence., 1949.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 743. Ladouceur residence
        Lubao Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections, perspective and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. Ladouceur.
      - Richards residence & garage., 1949.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 745. Richards residence & garage
        Oak Canyon Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details. Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Jack Richards.
      - Swanson residence & garage., 1949.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 752. Swanson residence & garage
        Leonora St. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations and sections.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Hugo Swanson.
      - Harvey residence., 1949.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 753. Harvey residence
        Berry Dr. Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. J. Harvey.
      - Schloen residence., 1949.; 5.; 8 items.
        Job Number 757. Schloen residence
        15725 Woodvale Rd. Sherman Woods, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. William Schloen Jr.
    - (3 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 129)
      - Buest residence & garage., 1949.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 762. Buest residence & garage
        San Bernardino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. M.C. Buest.
      - MacMillan residence., 1949.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 763. MacMillan residence
        Powhatan Rd. Apple Valley, Yucca Estates, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Don A. MacMillan.
      - Winchester dwelling & garage., 1949.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 764. Winchester dwelling & garage
        Cartwright St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F. I. Wonchester.
    - (4 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 130)
      - King Ranch house., 1949.; 1.; 34 items.
        Job Number 767. King Ranch house
        4425 Woodley Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John King.
      - Meyer/ Swanson residence., 1949.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 769. Meyer/ Swanson residence
        Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Shipstad.
    - (5 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 131)
      - Clark residence., 1949.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 771. Clark residence
        Camino de la Cumbre, Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Elvin Clark.
      - Robertson residence & garage., 1949.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 781. Robertson residence & garage
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F. Robertson.
      - Tomberlin residence., 1949.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 782. Tomberlin residence
        S. Beach St. Casper, Wyoming.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. B. Tomberlin.
      - Murray residence & Garage., 1949.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 783. Murray residence & Garage
        8808 Shoshone Ave. Northridge, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. G. Murray.
    - (6 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 132)
      - Blanchard residence & Garage., 1949.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 784. Blanchard residence & Garage
        Huston St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. W. Blanchard.
      - Madsen residence., 1949.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 788. Madsen residence
        4222 St. Clair, Studio City, CA.
        Owner: Mr. J.R. Madsen.
      - Grothers farmhouse., 1949.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 789. Grothers farmhouse
        17950 Rancho Dr. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, elevations and perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. H. H. Grothers.
      - Brown residence., 1949.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 790. Brown residence
        15014 Burbank Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections and elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. J. Brown.
      - Safarik residence & carport., 1949.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 791. Safarik residence & carport
        Woodman Ave.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. F. Safarik.
    - (7 of 7)., 1949 (Folder 133)
      - Crosby Ranch house., 1949.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 792. Crosby Ranch house
        5116 Sofia Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. O. C. Crosby.
      - Margrove residence., 1949.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 796. Margrove residence
        Hillview Park Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. Margrove.
      - Meyer residence., 1949.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 797. Meyer residence
        5803 Penfield Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F. W. Meyer Jr.
      - Miner residence & garage., 1949.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 803. Miner residence & garage
        4535 Encino Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, section and details.
      - Richardson "Hacienda"., 1949.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 805. Richardson "Hacienda"
        15490 Addison St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm Richardson.
    - (1 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 134)
      - Mawson Ranch house., 1950.; 32 items.
        Job Number 807. Mawson Ranch house
        Valley Vista St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. John F. Mawson.
    - (2 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 135)
      - Richards residence., 1950.; 1.; 13 items.
        Job Number 744. Richards residence
        Mulholland Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. D. Richards.
      - Swenson residence., 1950.; 2.; 9 items.
        Job Number 812, 891. Swenson residence
        White Oak Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: David Swenson.
      - Willoughby Howe Beach house., 1950.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 813. Willoughby Howe Beach house
        Playa del Rey, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations and a sketch on trace paper.
        Owner: Dr. J. Willoughby Howe.
    - (3 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 136)
      - Smith ranch house., 1950.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 816. Smith ranch house
        9112 Hazeltine Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harry Smith.
      - Cramer ranch house., 1950.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 818. Cramer ranch house
        19432 Collier St. Tarzana, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations and section.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. Cramer.
      - Moore residence & garage., 1950.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 819. Moore residence & garage
        2460 Canyon Oak Dr. Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Pat Moore.
      - McCandless "Colonial"., 1950-1951.; 4.; 16 items.
        Job Number 821, 881. McCandless "Colonial"
        Valley Vista Blvd. Sherman Woods, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Wm. McCandless.
    - (4 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 137)
      - Bowen Modern ranch., 1950.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 825. Bowen Modern ranch
        Collier St. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E. A. Bowen.
      - Vielle Modern Country., 1950.; 2.; 12 items.
        Job Number 833, 833A. Vielle Modern Country
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. A.C. Vielle.
      - Siegel residence., 1950.; 3.; 8 items.
        Job Number 834. Siegel residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Bert Siegel.
      - Hunter Modern Country., 1950.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 835. Hunter Modern Country
        Gresham St. Northridge, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. B.S. Hunter.
    - (5 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 138)
      - Crank "Hacienda"., 1950.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 838. Crank "Hacienda"
        Hawenhurst Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Fillmore Crank.
      - Madsen residence., 1950.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 839. Madsen residence
        Libbit Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. R. Madsen.
      - Ansaldi residence., 1950.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 840. Ansaldi residence
        14416 Valley Vista Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. V. Ansaldi.
      - Polster residence., 1950.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 841. Polster residence
        14318 Addison Ave. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. L. H. Polster.
      - Kipp residence., 1950.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 842. Kipp residence
        Owner: Kipp.
    - (6 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 139)
      - Lampke residence., 1950.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 843. Lampke residence
        Beckford Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, and elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. N. Lampke.
      - Vosganian residence., 1950.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 844. Vosganian residence
        Yolanda Ave. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Armenouhie Vosganian.
      - Haper residence., 1950.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 849. Haper residence
        14110 Valley Vista Blvd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Wm. Harper.
      - Couzens residence., 1950.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 852. Couzens residence
        5813 Lubao Ave. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Owner: Joseph H. & Helen F. Couzens.
      - Lowe residence., 1950.; 5.; 1 item.
        Job Number 854. Lowe residence
        21235 Lopez St. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Dan Lowe.
    - (7 of 7)., 1950 (Folder 140)
      - Jensen residence., 1950.; 1.; 1 item.
        Job Number 855. Jensen residence
        Albers St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harold Jensen.
      - Finsterwald Hilltopper., 1950.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 856. Finsterwald Hilltopper
        3911 Cody Rd. Val Aire Estates (Sherman Oaks), CA.
        Owner: Fred Finsterwald.
      - Tillman Hilltopper., 1950.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 856A, 64-15. Tillman Hilltopper
        3921 Cody Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Original and copy of drawings for residence and alterations and additions (64-15): plans, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Tillman.
      - Crosby ranch house., 1950.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 859. Crosby ranch house
        19456 Santa Rita St. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. O.C. Crosby.
      - Boye residence., 1950.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 860. Boye residence
        Wyandotte St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harold J. Boye.
    - (1 of 6)., 1951 (Folder 141)
      - Moss residence., 1951.; 1.; 1 item.
        Moss residence
        Original drawing: plans. Owner: Edith Moss.
      - Crawley residence., 1951.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 846. Crawley residence
        5011 Odessa Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Wayne O. & Ruth B. Crawley.
      - Walter residence., 1951.; 3.; 9 items.
        Job Number 862. Walter residence
        216 N. Glenroy Ave. W. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Robert S. Walter.
      - Freeman residence., 1951.; 4.; 13 items.
        Job Number 863. Freeman residence
        3965 Valley Meadow Rd. Royal Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Alwyn Freeman.
    - (2 of 6)., 1951 (Folder 142)
      - Doyle residence (2 of 6)., 1951.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 865. Doyle residence
        Rand Dr. Sherman oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. A.D.M. (Barney) Doyle.
      - Webb residence., 1951.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 867. Webb residence
        Radford Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. O. R. Webb.
      - Bobier residence., 1951.; 3.; 2 items.
        Job Number 873. Bobier residence
        Rand Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Harold & Bryce Bobier.
      - Biggy residence., 1951.; 4.; 1 item.
        Job Number 874. Biggy residence
        Sacton Sea, CA.
        Original drawing: plan, section, elevation.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F. Biggy.
      - Crawley residence., 1951.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 876. Crawley residence
        Otsego St. Encino, CA.
    - (3 of 6)., 1951 (Folder 143)
      - Rath residence., 1951.; 1.; 8 items.
        Job Number 877. Rath residence
        17655 Belinda St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. T. Rath Jr.
      - Stoddard residence., 1951.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 883. Stoddard residence
        Wells Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Russ Stoddard.
      - McAdams residence., 1951.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 887. McAdams residence
        3863 Cody Rd. Val Aire, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. McAdams.
      - Rizzuto residence., 1951.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 888. Rizzuto residence
        5455 Penfield Ave. Woodland Hills, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, section, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. Rizzuto.
      - Holden residence & carport., 1951.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 893. Holden residence & carport
        Rhodes St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Cyril M. Holden.
      - May Hillside residence., 1951.; 6.; 3 items.
        Job Number 895. May Hillside residence
        Avenida Del Sol. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Fritz May.
    - (4 of 6)., 1951 (Folder 144)
      - Madsen "Hacienda"., 1951.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 896. Madsen "Hacienda"
        Lido Isle, CA.
      - Faust Desert ranch., 1951.; 2.; 7 items.
        Job Number 898, 926. Faust Desert ranch
        Dead Man Pt. Apple Valley, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Marty Faust.
      - Lefevre residence., 1951.; 3.; 4 items.
        Job Number 901. Lefevre residence
        18638 Tarzana Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Owner: Louis Lefevre.
      - Madsen residence., 1951.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 903. Madsen residence
        Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J.R. Madsen.
      - Harrison residence., 1951.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 904. Harrison residence
        7014 Woodman Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Thos. Harrison.
    - (5 of 6)., 1951 (Folder 145)
      - Douglass Carter residence., 1951.; 1.; 3 items.
        Job Number 905. Douglass Carter residence
        Le Canada, CA.
        Owner: John Douglass & Jane Carter Fast.
      - Jordan residence., 1951.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 909. Jordan residence
        16116 Otsego St. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J.W. Jordan.
      - Markes residence., 1951.; 3.; 7 items.
        Job Number 914, 64-11. Markes residence
        4530 Gable D. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings for residence and alterations to residence (64-11): plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Larry Markes.
      - Carpenter duplex., 1951.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 915. Carpenter duplex
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E.O. Carpenter.
      - Finsterwald residence., 1951.; 5.; 6 items.
        Job Number 919, 920. Finsterwald residence
        Cody Rd. Sherman Oaks, CA.
    - (6 of 6)., 1951 (Folder 146)
      - Fox residence., 1951.; 1.; 7 items.
        Job Number 924. Fox residence
        5605 Hill Oak Dr. Los Angles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, section and perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Cort Fox.
      - Shimp Valley View residence., 1951.; 2.; 4 items.
        Job Number 927. Shimp Valley View residence
        Alomar Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harry E. Shimp.
      - Bender Small house., 1951.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 932. Bender Small house
        Moorpark St. North Hollywood, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, elevations and detail.
      - Thatcher residence., 1951.; 4.; 7 items.
        Job Number 933, 56-17. Thatcher residence
        3110 Brookdale Rd. Studio City, CA.
        Original drawings for residence and alterations to residence (56-17): plans, interior and exterior elevations, sections and details.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. George Thatcher.
    - (1 of 5)., 1952 (Folder 147)
      - Hart Beach house., 1952.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 800. Hart Beach house
        Vialido Sound.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harry Hart.
      - West residence., 1952.; 2.; 11 items.
        Job Number 921. West residence
        Mt. Lowe, Bakersfield, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations, section, details and perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Geo. F. West.
      - Kimes residence., 1952.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 925, 925-A. Kimes residence
        14023 Weddington St. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. N. Kimes.
    - (2 of 5)., 1952 (Folder 148)
      - Parker Colonial estate., 1952.; 1.; 21 items.
        Job Number 934. Parker Colonial estate
        Original drawings: plans, exterior and interior elevations, sections, details and perspective.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Warren K. Parker.
      - Craig residence., 1952.; 2.; 5 items.
        Job Number 935. Craig residence
        Whipple Ave. Toluca Lake, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. N. L. Craig.
      - Springsteen residence., 1952.; 3.; 1 item.
        Job Number 936? Springsteen residence
        Royal Oaks Estates, Sherman Oaks, CA. Original drawing: elevation. Owner: Mr. & Mrs. R. G. Springsteen.
      - Luce "Frontier" residence., 1952.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 937. Luce "Frontier" residence
        Larue Ave. Reno, Nevada.
        Original drawings: plans, perspective, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harold Luce.
    - (3 of 5)., 1952 (Folder 149)
      - Stoddard residence., 1952.; 1.; 6 items.
        Job Number 939. Stoddard residence
        Garvin Drive, Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. R. L. Stoddard.
      - Stockl residence., 1952.; 2.; 6 items.
        Job Number 940. Stockl residence
        Havenhurst Ave. Encino, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, sections, perspective, interior and exterior elevations.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Karl Stockl.
      - Jordan residence., 1952.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 942. Jordan residence
        Del Gado Dr. Sherman Oaks, CA.
        Owner: Mr. J. W. Jordan.
      - Flier "Tackle House"., 1952.; 4.; 2 items.
        Job Number 943. Flier "Tackle House"
        12833 Ventura Blvd. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Shelly Flier.
      - Mark residence., 1952.; 5.; 2 items.
        Job Number 946. Mark residence
        4718 Petit, Encino, CA.
        Original drawing: plans, elevations, details and perspectives.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. J. S. Mark.
      - Knox residence., 1952.; 6.; 4 items.
        Job Number 947. Knox residence
        6133 S. Bonsal Dr. Los Angeles County, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Harvey Knox.
    - (4 of 5)., 1952 (Folder 150)
      - Eiklor residence., 1952.; 1.; 5 items.
        Job Number 948. Eiklor residence
        Hollyoak Dr. Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W. K. Eiklor.
      - Jordan residence., 1952.; 2.; 2 items.
        Job Number 949. Jordan residence
        13330 Chandler Blvd. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. J. W. Jordan.
      - Chet Crank residence., 1952.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 953. Chet Crank residence
        Kimridge Rd. Los Angeles, CA.
        Owner: Chet Crank.
      - Slavin residence (4 of 5)., 1952.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 955. Slavin residence
        14001 Weddington St. Van Nuys, CA.
    - (5 of 5)., 1952 (Folder 151)
      - Hallstad duplex., 1952.; 1.; 2 items.
        Job Number 956. Hallstad duplex
        Beck Ave. North Hollywood, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. W. Hallsted.
      - Licker residence., 1952.; 2.; 9 items.
        Job Number 958. Licker residence
        Petit Ave. Encino, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Licker.
      - Gallagher residence., 1952.; 3.; 3 items.
        Job Number 967. Gallagher residence
        5522 Allott Ave. Van Nuys, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. T.M. Gallagher.
      - Johnston residence., 1952.; 4.; 3 items.
        Job Number 970. Johnston residence
        2619 Wilshire Blvd. Los Angeles, CA.
      - Kuznetsky residence., 1952.; 5.; 3 items.
        Job Number 979. Kuznetsky residence
        Topeka Dr. Tarzana, CA.
        Original Drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations and details.
        Owner: Dr. & Mrs. Chas. A. Kuznetsky.
      - Shaw "Colonial Trails" residence., 1952.; 6.; 7 items.
        Job Number 983. Shaw "Colonial Trails" residence
        Royal Oaks, CA.
        Perspectives.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. E. B. Shaw.
    - (1 of 5)., 1953 (Folder 152)
      - Myers residence., 1953.; 1.; 4 items.
        Job Number 989. Myers residence
        Twin Oaks Rd. Hidden Hills, Calabasas, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. William Myes.
      - Branch residence., 1953.; 2.; 3 items.
        Job Number 990. Branch residence
        Via Alta, Burbank, CA.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. Chas. W. Branch.
      - Cornelius residence., 1953.; 3.; 6 items.
        Job Number 991. Cornelius residence
        10059 Lindbrook Dr. West Los Angeles, CA.
        Original drawings: plans, interior and exterior elevations and sections.
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. G. S. Cornelius.
      - Brahms residence., 1953.; 4.; 4 items.
        Job Number 992. Brahms residence
        2254 Stradella Rd. Bel Air Highlands, CA.
        Owner: H. Robert Brahms.
      - McLaughlin residence., 1953.; 5.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-5. McLaughlin residence
        Owner: Mr. & Mrs. F. G. McLaughlin.
      - Soutter residence., 1953.; 6.; 5 items.
        Job Number 53-9. Soutter residence
        Bel Air Rd. Bel Air, CA.